Hey, this is Tracy Goodwin and I'm the red sweater lady.
And I'm here to talk to you about having a very successful job interview.
And I'm talking about the actual interview itself.
Now I don't know if you knew this or not, but there are three phases in an actual interview.
You have what is called the warm-up, the question and answer stage, and the closing.
And we're going to talk about all of those and what is important to each and every phase.
Also going to take a look at what happens after the interview.
What happens during the interview with regards to information that you want to find out and information the employer is going to find out from you.
Lots of important tips and strategies for make the absolute best impression that you can at the interview.
Which is very important in such a competitive job market that we live with today.
You made it this far.
Your resume and your qualifications were impressive enough to get you to this point.
Now, we really want to do a bang up job at the interview so that you can get that job offer that you want.